(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
ときのそら お披露目誕生日 2026
告知あり
[Title: Tokino Sora Birthday Reveal 2026]
[Announcement included]
高鳴る心臓に祈りを乗せて
Place a prayer on the pounding heart
曖昧な夢を描く
Draw an ambiguous dream
幻想は想像のまま
The illusion remains just as imagination
終われないんだ
It cannot end
Diva
作詞・作曲・編曲：Aira(Dream Monster)
Lyrics, Music, & Arrangement: Aira (Dream Monster)
みんな今日見に来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for coming to see me today!
答えを延々と探し続けて
Continuing to search for the answer endlessly
何者かになりたくて
Wanting to become someone
潸々と降る夕立を
The evening shower falling in torrents,
ただ眺めた
I just watched it
優しく寄り添って
If you gently nestle close
心が晴れるのなら
And the heart clears up
翼が生えたような気がして
I feel like I've grown wings
いつだって隣にいるから
Because you're always by my side
だって言葉紡いで唄うことが
Because spinning words and singing
わたしの運命だ
is my destiny
世界にありふれた虚しささえも
Even overwriting the common emptiness
上書きして
in the world
路地裏に咲いた花のように
Like a flower blooming in the back alley
願いを照らす
It illuminates wishes
小さな光に憧れて
Longing for a small light
名前を持たない歌なんて
A song with no name
神様は認めてくれない
God won't acknowledge it
一つ一つ枯れない花のよう
Like flowers that never fade, one by one
昨日の自分にさよならして
Saying goodbye to my yesterday's self
溢れた涙
Overflowing tears
うまく笑えなくてもいいかな
It's okay if I can't smile well, right?
だって理想は遠ざかってくばかり
Because ideals just keep getting further away
もう散々だよ
It's already a disaster
どれだけ手を伸ばして叫んだって
No matter how much I reach out and shout
届かないの
It doesn't reach
望めばいつか叶うはずって信じてる
I believe that if I wish, it will come true someday
どうか 歌よ響いて
Please, let the song resonate
あぁ心臓の鼓動が今日も五月蝿い
Ah, the beating of my heart is noisy again today
[曲：Diva]
[Song: Diva]
行き止まりばっか足が竦んで立てないよ
I'm blocked, my feet tremble and I can't stand
音のない世界から君を見つけて連れ出すんだ
I'll find you in a soundless world and take you out
言葉紡いで唄うことがわたしの運命だ
Singing by weaving words is my destiny
世界にありふれた虚しささえも上書きして
Overwriting the common emptiness in the world
路地裏に咲いた花のように
Like a flower blooming in a back alley
願いを照らす小さな光に憧れて
Longing for a small light to illuminate my wish
君の歌姫になれたらいいな
I wish I could be your diva
[曲：Dancing Reed]
[Song: Dancing Reed]
Okey Dokey 返事はいいけど冗談なら笑えないよ
Okey dokey, a reply is fine but jokes aren't funny
渋滞 曖昧 どっちを向いちゃうの
Stuck in traffic or unsure, which way will you go?
蜃気楼に手を伸ばした
I stretched my hand out towards a mirage
微熱のような夢物語
A feverish, dreamlike tale
そんな光は見ない振りしていた
I pretended not to see that kind of light
ざわめく鼓動 まだ行かないで
My restless heartbeat, don’t leave yet
幻じゃ嫌だよ
I don’t want it to be an illusion
私を奪って
Take me away
魅惑のDancing Dancing night
Alluring dancing, dancing night
拡がって収まんない Universe
Expanding, unstoppable universe
君の表情は 私の森羅万象を
Your expression might rewrite my entire world,
書き換えちゃうかも 責任重大ね
it's a big responsibility
一切合切
Anything and everything
Dance Dance Dance We Are Dancing Reed
夢中になって絡み合った ゼログラビティ
Excited and entangled in zero gravity
構わず
Not caring
Dance Dance Dance Just a Dance Just a Dance
声は闇に預けたまま
Leaving my voice to the darkness
目を覚ましても離れないで
Even if you open your eyes, don’t leave me
Maybe Needy 正気じゃないのよ
Maybe needy, I’m not in my right mind
体温が忘れられない
I won’t forget your body heat
誰 彼 そんなじゃないから
That’s not the case for everyone
独り占めしてEuphoria
Monopolizing you, euphoria
気にしてない様な 言葉は装飾で
Words that seem like I don’t care are decoration
メイクの様には流せない
It can’t be wiped away like makeup
360°偽りだって
Even if it’s 360° lies
隠しきれぬような
When I can’t hide myself
私に構って 嬉しいなんて
You care for me and it makes me happy
Crazy Crazy Love
摩天楼から連れさらって
Take me away from the skyscrapers
君の表情は 私の深層心理を
Your expression replaces my subconscious,
すり替えちゃうのよ 責任重大ね
it’s a big responsibility
過ぎ去ったネオン
The passing neon
残像 Shooting Star
Afterimage of a shooting star
グライダーみたいに漂えば
Floating like a glider
幸も不幸もなかった
There was no joy or sorrow
指先でまた君を探している
Looking for you with my fingertips
その声を聴かせてよ
Let me hear your voice
私に構って
Pay attention to me
教えてよ恋の先を！
Tell me where this love is going!
拡がって収まんない Universe
Expanding, unstoppable universe
君の存在は 私の将来までも
Your existence has reached into my future,
踏み込んだのよ 付き合ってよね
go out with me
一切合切
Anything and everything
Dance Dance Dance We Are Dancing Reed
夢中になって絡み合った ゼログラビティ
Excited and entangled in zero gravity
構わず
Not caring
Dance Dance Dance Just a Dance Just a Dance
声は闇に預けたまま
Leaving my voice to the darkness
目を覚ましても離れないで
Even if you open your eyes, don’t leave me
みんなー！今日は誕生日ライブに来てくれてありがとー！
Everyone! Thank you for coming to my birthday live today!
コメントも見えてるよー！
I can see the comments too!
最初に聴いてもらったのが、Diva、Dancing Reedでした！
The first songs you heard were Diva and Dancing Reed!
2026... ときのそらお披露目誕生日2026！
2026... Tokino Sora Debut Birthday 2026!
あ、ときのそらおじゃ... じゃないよ、ときのそらだよ！
Wait, not Tokino Sora-oja... it's Tokino Sora!
みんなのつぶやきを待ってるので、たくさんつぶやいてほしいな！
I'm waiting for everyone's tweets, so please tweet a lot!
トレンドに入るといいな！
I hope it trends!
ねー！
Right?!
今回のテーマは、8周年を象徴する「無限」をモチーフに...
The theme this time is based on "Infinity," symbolizing the 8th anniversary...
宇宙や星をステージに散りばめて、中毒性のあるビートやリズムで構成した...
...with stars and space scattered across the stage, featuring addictive beats and rhythms...
デジタルパルスライブです！
...it's the Digital Pulse Live!
デジタルパルスライブ！
Digital Pulse Live!
大きな天球が曲によってどう変わるのかを見ていてください。
Please watch how the large celestial sphere changes with each song.
今年ののんのんは5つなので、くるくる回転してます。
There are five Non-Nons this year, so they're spinning around.
くるくるくるくる...
Spinning, spinning...
そして、空にはそらざうるすもいるよ！
And there's a Sorasaurus in the sky too!
そらざうるすはね、なんと炎を出せるようになりました！
Sorasaurus can now actually breathe fire!
ぷぉー！
Whoosh!
あんきもも、ちゃんとあんきもざも、あるんですけど、見えるかな？
Ankimo is here, and there's an Ankimoz too, can you see them?
今年も新衣装のお披露目や、告知したゲストとのパフォーマンスなど...
Look forward to the new outfit reveal and performances with our guests...
どんな曲を披露するのかを楽しみにしていてくださいね！
...and see what kind of songs we'll be performing!
そして、次に行く前に、ぷちお披露目、最初にしちゃいましょう！
But before we move on, let's do a mini-reveal first!
みなさん、上を見てください！
Everyone, please look up!
ときのそら お披露目誕生日 2026
[Title: Tokino Sora Debut Birthday 2026]
新しいクラゲヘア、新髪型お披露目です！
It's my new jellyfish hair reveal!
それでは早速、ゲストパート、いってみよう！
Now then, let's head straight into the guest segment!
かわいい、ありがとう！おお、かわいい、ありがとう！
So cute? Thank you! Oh, thank you!
シロコメさんもいっぱいコメントしててね！
Shiro-kome, please leave lots of comments too!
最初のゲストは、この人です！
Our first guest is this person!
電脳少女シロ
[Guest: Denno Shoujo Siro]
星の降るたびに 恋をするたびに
Every time the stars fall, every time I fall in love
バイバイ だって、夜はギャラクティカ
Bye bye, because the night is a Galactica
明星ギャラクティカ
[Song: Myoushou Galactica]
今夜は宇宙の アイオライトが
Tonight, the iolite of the universe
いやに眩しいから
Is dazzlingly bright, so
街のネオンからも 星やどり 何処か
From the city's neon lights, finding shelter in the stars
逃げようかふたり
Shall we run away somewhere, the two of us?
しどけないくらい 揺らぐグラスが
The glass swaying a little too carelessly
心惑わすから
Confuses my heart, so
あなただけ 君だけ 今夜だけ
Only you, just you, just tonight
夜に星梯子掛ける
I'll set up a ladder to the stars in the night
見つめ あなたの表情
Stare at your expression
照らして明星 ギャラクティカ
Illuminate it, Myoushou Galactica
見上げた あなたの 瞳が 宇宙が
Looking up, your eyes, the universe
キラキラって光る
Are sparkling and shining
近づく程にホードン
Hold on, the closer we get
ねえ孤独ごと抱きしめて
Hey, hold me together with my loneliness
ふたりの 銀河で 手と手が 星と星が
In our galaxy, hand in hand, star to star
交わって 恋はギャラクティカ
They cross, love is a Galactica
嗚呼、同じペースで 泳ぎだすペーヴメント
Ah, swimming out at the same pace, on the pavement
宵と宵でつなぐ朝へ 一度きりのラブ
Connecting night to night, towards the morning, a once-in-a-lifetime love
あなたとわたしの 灯す星の行方は
Where is the star we light together pointing?
何光年先を指した
How many light-years ahead?
結ぶオリオンの 愛の星が
The love star of the connected Orion
真っ赤に燃えるから
Is burning bright red, so
今夜だけ 君だけ 踊りましょう
Just tonight, just you, let's dance
夜は 天邪鬼だから
Because the night is a rebellious spirit
見つめ あなたの表情
Stare at your expression
隠して明星 ギャラクティカ
Hide it, Myoushou Galactica
そのときめいた 気持ちが 未知だって
That pounding feeling is unknown, so
手探りでいいから
It's okay to feel our way through
生まれたままの衝動
The primitive impulse
隠して明星 ギャラクティカ
Hide it, Myoushou Galactica
わたしの あなたの 鼓動が 鼓動が
My, your heartbeat, heartbeat
ドキドキって疾る
Is pounding fast
壊れる程にホードン
Hold on, until it breaks
本当のこと言わないで
Don't tell me the truth
最後の 夜明けは 手と手が 星と星が
In the final dawn, hand in hand, star to star
ほどけて 君はギャラクティカ
They come apart, and you are a Galactica
いつだって、愛はロマンティカ
Love is always a Romantica
パッパッパーヤ パッパパパーヤ
Pa-pa-pa-paya, pa-pa-pa-paya
はい！というわけで最初のゲストは、シロちゃんだよ！
Yes! So, our first guest is Shiro-chan!
こんにちは！電脳少女...ときのシロです！
Hello! I'm Cyber... Tokino Shiro!
本当に今日はそらちゃん、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Sora-chan, happy birthday to you today, really!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
すごいね、格好。
That's quite an outfit.
あ、そらちゃんという歌姫にお会いできると聞いて...
Ah, hearing I could meet a diva like Sora-chan...
出せるものは全部出していこうと思います。
I thought I'd show everything I've got.
そ、そういうことだったんだ。待って、これでチャンネルBANしちゃったら...
O-Oh, so that's what it was. Wait, if the channel gets banned for this...
そんなことないよ！ごめんなさい、大丈夫、大丈夫！
That won't happen! I'm sorry, it's okay, it's okay!
大丈夫？胸が苦しくなってきました。
Are you okay? My chest is starting to feel tight.
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
そらちゃん、クラゲさんには毒針があると聞きます。
Sora-chan, I hear jellyfish have poisonous stingers.
毒針？
Poisonous stingers?
毒針をぜひ、頭でごちゅんと後ろに刺していただけませんか？
Could you please sting me in the back with your head? Just a little 'gochun'!
ふふ...ごちゅん！
Hehe... Gochun!
うっ...倒れる、倒れちゃう...
Ugh... I'm falling, I'm gonna fall...
うわぁ、すごい効いてきました。
Wow, it's really starting to work.
効いてきた？
It's working?
皆さん、そらちゃんは変わりました。毒針を持った女に変わったんです！
Everyone, Sora-chan has changed. She's changed into a woman with a poisonous stinger!
何それ？でもそう、私強くなったから。
What's that? But yeah, I've become stronger.
そらちゃんは毒針が持ちたくて、可愛いクラゲヘアになったんですか？
Did you choose the cute jellyfish hair because you wanted a stinger?
いやいや、私やっぱアイドルといえばこういう可愛い髪型の人が多いかなと思って、そういうアイドルっぽい髪型にしちゃおっかなと思ってたんだよね。
No, no, I just thought idols usually have cute hairstyles like this, so I thought I'd go with an idol-like hairstyle.
はぁ...そらちゃんって聞いてください。何もう...アイドルでしかないし、歌姫でしかないのに...
Sigh... Sora-chan, please listen. She's nothing but an idol, nothing but a diva...
Divaって曲も出してますけど、今もアイドルであろうとこう...なってるもんね。
Even with her song 'Diva', she's still striving to be an idol like this.
努力してくれる姿がもう大好きで食べたいくらい。
I love how she works so hard, I could almost eat her up.
食べちゃうの？
You're gonna eat me?
シナモロールみたいですね。見て、カメラさん、見て見て！
She's like a Cinnamoroll. Look, cameraman, look, look!
これはシナモロール？
Is this Cinnamoroll?
シナモロール...食べられてる、食べられてる。
Cinnamoroll... I'm being eaten, I'm being eaten.
いい匂い...どう？
Smells good... How about it?
あはは、いい匂いですね。
Ahaha, it does smell good.
はい！ということで、今日はBANされない発言を心がけていきます！
Yes! So, I'll do my best to avoid saying anything that gets us banned!
もうすでに結構シロちゃんワールド炸裂してますけど。
The Shiro-chan world is already in full swing, though.
あの、なんかこんな大好きなそらちゃんのこんな場に、そらともさんたちと一緒に呼んでもらえると思わなくて。ありがとう！
I never thought I'd be invited to such a place for my beloved Sora-chan, along with all the Soratomos. Thank you!
3年ぶりだよ！
It's been three years!
3年ぶりの元カノです。元カノじゃない！
I'm the ex-girlfriend after three years. Not an ex-girlfriend!
そらともさん、一緒に、一緒に！独り占めしないので愛でていきましょう。
Soratomos, let's cherish her together! I won't keep her to myself.
あの、今日はそらともさんに、シロの期待意味を分からせたいと思います。
Today, I want to show the Soratomos the meaning of Shiro's expectations.
そらちゃん、立ってください。
Sora-chan, please stand up.
はい。
Okay.
3, 2, 1... バニーガールです！
3, 2, 1... Bunny girl!
このスクリーンショットでいいの？ねぇ？
Is this screenshot okay? Really?
千手観音！千手観音！
Thousand-Armed Kannon! Thousand-Armed Kannon!
そらちゃん新衣装のバニー衣装プレゼントしに来ました。
I came to present Sora-chan's new bunny outfit.
ありがとう！どうですか？可愛いよ、バニーガールも可愛いよ！
Thank you! How is it? It's cute, the bunny girl is cute too!
うさぎさんって万年発情してるので、ちょっとはぁはぁしてもらって...
Rabbits are always in heat, so could you do a little 'ha-ha'...
可愛いーー！
So cute--!
私も尻尾あるよ！
I have a tail too!
そうだよ、そらちゃんと言えば尻尾は...さぁ、ちょっと押してもいいですか？
That's right, speaking of Sora-chan, her tail is... well, can I push it a bit?
いいよ。
Sure.
ちゅンちゅん... あっ！大変！
Chun-chun... Oh no!
何？シロ、発情が止まらないので、そろそろおうちに帰ります。
What? Shiro's heat won't stop, so I'm going home soon.
帰っちゃうの？
You're leaving?
月から皆を見守っています。このあとも楽しんでね！ありがとう！
I'll be watching over everyone from the moon. Enjoy the rest! Thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
パッパッパッパッパッ...
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa...
本当に...あ、なんか出てきた...あ、
Really... oh, something came out... oh,
ちょっと！帰れてないよ！
Wait! You haven't made it back yet!
シロちゃんワールド炸裂で楽しかったね。何だこれって言わないで皆、ねぇ？けど相変わらずのシロちゃんで、一緒に歌えてとっても楽しかったです。
The Shiro-chan world was a blast. Don't ask 'What was that?', everyone, okay? But she's still the same Shiro-chan, and it was so much fun singing with her.
マイペースだね、マイペースだよ。私もマイペースだから、いいコンビってことだ！
She goes at her own pace. I go at mine too, so we're a good team!
というわけで、続いてのゲストに行きましょう。この人です！
So then, let's move on to the next guest. It's this person!
ときのそら お披露目誕生日 2020
[Title: Tokino Sora Birthday Party 2020]
緋月ゆい
[Guest: Hizuki Yui]
いきますよー
Here we go!
ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
作詞・作曲: Amala
[Song: Dai Dai Dai Dai Dai Kirai]
[Lyrics/Composition: Amala]
全部 全部 アンタのせいだ
It's all, all your fault.
反吐が出るくらいにウザったいわ
You're such a pain, it makes me wanna hurl.
何かに縋って諂って
Clinging to things, fawning over things...
期待したアタシが馬鹿だった
I was stupid to think I'd get something out of it.
ご機嫌伺いの八方美人
I'm a people-pleaser coming to pay my respects,
それ故にアンチな一生Gimme
So gimme an hater life.
浅いキャパシティ まいどおおきに
I've got a shallow capacity, thanks for your patronage.
つまるとこ 人生ずっと地味
Basically, my life's always been drab.
｢憎たらしい！｣｢痛々しい！｣
"How hateful! How pathetic!"
無視出来ないのが一層
The way I can't ignore you makes it worse-
腹立たしい 苛立たしい
How maddening, how vexing.
そろそろ飽きた 自画自賛に (Look around!!)
I've had just about enough of blowing my own horn. (Look around!!)
ライクの反対はアパシー ≒ 繋がれた証
The opposite of like is apathy ≈ proof that you're connected.
切り離せない関係 逸らしてしまいたいわ
A relationship I can't cut off... I'd love to just look away from it.
これは所謂 ヘイトスピーチ
This is what you'd call hate speech.
匿名性の声明を生命に載せてんだ
We're slapping these anonymous declarations onto our very lives.
鳴り止まないサイレン 近づく度に痙攣
We spasm every time those ceaseless sirens draw near.
赤信号にずっと従順です。
We've obeyed red lights all this time.
大体 アナタのコト アタシ ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
Point is, 'bout you, I absolutely--hate hate hate hate hate you.
OMG 情けない 最早 バイバイバイバイバイしたい
OMG, how pathetic, I just wanna say--bye bye bye bye bye already.
脳内も予測不能 故に 解解解解解は無い
Can't predict what's going on in that mind, and thus there's--no no no no no solution.
どうだい？アタシのコト アナタ ダイダイダイダイダイキライになった？
How's it? 'Bout me, do you absolutely--hate hate hate hate me now?
あァ 百害あって一利ナシ Nothing Not see
Ah, all pain and no gain, nothing, not see.
もしタラレバ並べてもニコチンだし
It'd be like nicotine to think back on the what-ifs.
I miss youって近付いた結末は凡ミス 凡ミス
Getting close because "I miss you," was a stupid mistake, mistake.
センキュー 反面教師 後味 一生消えてくんないわ
Thanks for being a great bad example. You've left an aftertaste that won't ever disappear.
よしよし いい子ね 笑顔振り撒き パラパラ いい子ね
Good, good, you're a good girl, smiling and spreading yourself around, good girl,
だけど だけど その本性は？
but, but what's your true nature?
善悪の区別も付かないの？笑 はぁ。
Can't you even tell right from wrong? LOL, sigh.
減点方式で取り巻く環境に巻かれて
Winding myself up in an environment based on a point-deduction system,
生涯、痛い！痛い！痛い！も聞かれないわ！って
My "It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!" won't be heard for a lifetime,
当然の報いにクラっちゃった
I got hit by the inevitable retribution.
人は鏡なんです
People are mirrors.
実のところ 依存は両辺です
In truth, dependency is on both sides.
シャットダウンしても付き纏う 己の弱さが不甲斐ない
Even if I shut down, I'm haunted by my own pathetic weakness.
全部 全部 アンタのせいって 反吐が出るくらいに 止まんないわ
It's all, all your fault, I can't stop feeling... like I'm gonna hurl.
いっその事 切り離せた方が楽なのにな
It'd be so much easier if I could just cut it off.
大体 アナタのコト アタシ ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
Point is, 'bout you, I absolutely--hate hate hate hate hate you.
OMG 情けない 最早 バイバイバイバイバイしたい
OMG, how pathetic, I just wanna say--bye bye bye bye bye already.
脳内も予測不能 故に 解解解解解は無い
Can't predict what's going on in that mind, and thus there's--no no no no no solution.
どうだい？アタシのコト アナタ ダイダイダイダイダイキライになった？
How's it? 'Bout me, do you absolutely--hate hate hate hate me now?
あァ 百害あって一利ナシ Nothing Not see
Ah, all pain and no gain, nothing, not see.
もしタラレバ並べてもニコチンだし
It'd be like nicotine to think back on the what-ifs.
I miss youって近付いた結末は凡ミス 凡ミス
Getting close because "I miss you," was a stupid mistake, mistake.
センキュー 反面教師 後味 一生消えてくんないわ
Thanks for being a great bad example. You've left an aftertaste that won't ever disappear.
イェーイ！ありがとうございましたー！
Yeah! Thank you so much!
というわけでゲスト、はい、ユイちゃんです！
And so, our guest is... yes, it's Yui-chan!
はい、改めましてネオポルテ所属の緋月ゆいです。そらさん、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Hi, once again, I'm Hizuki Yui from Neo-Porte. Sora-san, happy birthday!
ありがとうございます！来てくれて嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy you came!
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
一年ぶり！
It's been a year!
A year!
いやね、去年はね、ちょっと残念ながらメッセージだけということだったんですけど...
Well, last year, unfortunately, it was just a message...
あ、どうも... あの、去年は本当に申し訳ございませんでした...
Oh, right... Um, I'm really sorry about last year...
いやメッセージでもね、すごくみんな「わー！」ってなってて、すごい嬉しかったですよ。
No, even with the message, everyone was like "Wow!", so I was really happy.
すごいガラガラ声でね、去年は...
With such a raspy voice last year...
お茶目になっちゃったね。
You were being playful.
参加させていただいたんですけれども、今年はリベンジができてとっても嬉しいです！
I participated, but I'm so happy I could have my revenge this year!
やったー！リベンジだー！
Yay! It's revenge!
呼んでいただいて嬉しいです。ありがとうございます！
I'm happy to be invited. Thank you!
こちらこそ！今回の曲もね、私が選んだんですけど...
Likewise! I chose this song as well...
やっぱりあの、ゆいちゃんといえばカッコいい声っていうのがね、すごく私の中で、もう頭の中にあった、やっぱカッコいいよ！
But you know, when I think of Yui-chan, I think of that cool voice, it was just in my head, it's so cool!
えー、本当ですか？
Really?
なので、このデュエットっていうのもあるので、この曲をぜひ一緒に歌いたいと思ってオファーしました。
So, since it's a duet, I really wanted to sing this song together and made the offer.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
どうだったかな？
How was it?
いや、あの、歌も超難しかったんですけど、どちらかというとダンスが普段あんまりしないので...
Well, the song was super hard, but more than that, I don't usually dance much...
そうだよね！
That's true!
はい、そらそらとダンスレッスンなどもやらせていただきましてですね...
Yes, I got to do dance lessons and such with Sora-sora...
したのしたの！
We did, we did!
この本番に向けて準備してまいりました。
And I prepared for this performance.
ね！でも振り覚えめちゃくちゃ早くてびっくりした！
Right! But I was surprised by how fast you learned the moves!
いえいえ、恐縮でございます。ちょっとね「あーっ」って言いながら回ってたの。
No, no, I'm flattered. I was turning around while going "Ahhh".
そうなの！
Is that so!
間奏でターンするところがあったんですけど、皆さん、ターンが本当に体幹がなさすぎて「あーっ」
There was a part where we turn during the interlude, and everyone, my core was so weak that I stumbled...
「あーっ」って何回もよろけてですね、大変だったんですけど...
...going "Ahhh" "Ahhh" and stumbled many times, it was hard...
いや、でも本番は完璧だったんじゃないの？
But wasn't it perfect during the real thing?
あ、よかったです。
Oh, that's good.
いや素晴らしいよ！
No, it was wonderful!
よかったー。よろけなくて。めっちゃ頭で「よろけんじゃねー、よろけんじゃねー」と思いながら...
Thank goodness. I didn't stumble. In my head I was thinking "Don't stumble, don't stumble"...
めっちゃよろけないようにっていうことを考えながら...
Thinking so hard about not stumbling...
意識しちゃうよね！
You do become conscious of it!
意識してました。そらさんが完璧なんで、ダンスが...
I was conscious. Because Sora-san is perfect at dancing...
いやいや、そんなことない！
No, no, not at all!
いやいや、全然そんなことないから！隣立つから、私もよろけないようにしないとって思って。
No, no, not at all! Since I'm standing next to you, I thought I had to make sure I don't stumble.
うまくいってよかったです。
I'm glad it went well.
本当に私も。まさかね、ダンスまでしてくれると思わなかったの。
Me too, really. I never thought you'd even dance for us.
だから、誘った時に「ダンスもあるんですけど…」って言った時に、
So when I invited you and said, "There's also dancing..."
「あぁ、ちょっと…」ってなるかなと思ったから。
I thought you might say, "Oh, I don't know about that..."
「ぜひ！」と思いまして。
I thought, "Definitely!"
普段ね、右手に、右手でどうにかしてるんで。
Usually, I just manage somehow with my right hand.
手持ちマイクで右手でどうにか尺稼ぎしてたんですけど、
I was just trying to kill time with a handheld mic in my right hand,
今日はダンスに挑戦できたのが、自分的にもすごく嬉しかったです。
but I was really happy that I could challenge myself with dancing today.
めちゃくちゃかっこよかった！
It was so cool!
一緒に踊れて超嬉しかったんで。
I was super happy to dance together.
私も嬉しかった！
I was happy too!
ありがとうございました。ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much. Thank you!
どうでしたか？どうだった！？
How was it? What did you think!?
かっこよかったでしょう！頑張ったぞ！
It was cool, right? We worked hard!
頑張ったよ！
We did our best!
このあともね、まだライブがあるということなので、
There's still more of the live show to come,
このあともぜひ頑張ってください！
so please keep doing your best for the rest!
頑張るよ！応援してます！
I will! I'm rooting for you!
ありがとうございました！緋月ゆいちゃんでした！
Thank you very much! That was Hizuki Yui-chan!
ありがとうございました！頑張ってね！
Thank you! Good luck!
ありがとね！バイバーイ！
Thanks! Bye-bye!
ということで、緋月ちゃんが来てくれました。
And so, Hizuki-chan came to visit.
「緋月ちゃん」って言ったの初めてかも。ゆいちゃんが来てくれました。嬉しいね。
That might be the first time I called her "Hizuki-chan." Yui-chan came. I'm so happy.
というわけで、あっという間なんだけど、私口癖「というわけで」なんだな。今気づいちゃった。
So, it's gone by in a flash, but I just realized my catchphrase is "And so..."
ここからライブ後半戦です。
From here begins the second half of the live.
それでは、5曲目聴いてください。
Now then, please listen to the fifth song.
モニタリング。
Monitoring.
ねえあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know,
きみがひとり“涙”してるの知ってるよ
I know you're crying alone.
ビクンビクン震えてさ
Trembling and twitching,
声もダダ漏れなんだわ
your voice is leaking out.
正直に言っちゃえばバレてるんだし
Just be honest, you've been found out anyway,
言っちゃえば効いてんの？
so say it, is it working?
普通普通 平気だよ
It's normal, normal, it's okay.
みんな分かってないだけ
Everyone's just not understanding it.
モニタリング (Best Friend Remix) / 作詞・作曲：DECO*27
[Song: Monitoring (Best Friend Remix) / Lyrics & Music: DECO*27]
ねえ、大丈夫？
Hey, are you okay?
心配だから今から助けに行くね！
I'm worried, so I'm coming to help you now!
ねえあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know,
きみがひとり“涙”してるの知ってるよ
I know you're crying alone.
グスングスン凹んでさ 弱音ヒトカラ in the night
Sniffling and depressed, singing your weakness alone in the night.
朝が来るまで一緒コース もっと泣いたって
Staying together until morning, cry even more if you want.
何度だって受け止めてあげる
I'll catch it every time for you.
もう我慢しないでいっぱい吐いてね
Don't hold it in anymore, just let it all out.
MWAH! お願い きみが欲しいの
MWAH! Please, I want you.
慰めさせて ベストフレンド 愛の才能で
Let me comfort you, Best Friend, with the talent of love.
泣いてくれるかい？ きみの辛い抱きしめたい ねえいいでしょう？
Will you cry for me? I want to embrace your pain, hey, it's okay, right?
わけあって乗り越えたいんだったたてば
I want to share it and overcome it.
MWAH! お願い きみが欲しいの
MWAH! Please, I want you.
笑い飛ばしてホップステップ さあ最高で
Laugh it off, hop step, it's the best.
泣いてくれるかい？ きみに重い不安や悩み ねえいいでしょう？
Will you cry for me? Your heavy anxieties and worries, hey, it's okay, right?
寄り添って救いたいんだったたてば
I want to stay by your side and save you.
見たい見たい見たい...
I want to see, want to see, want to see...
...の きみの中
...inside of you.
ねえあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know,
きみがひとり悔しがってんの知ってるよ
I know you're frustrated alone.
グスングスン終わるまで きみを決して諦めない
Until the sniffling ends, I will never give up on you.
ねえあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know,
きみはできる子 知ってるよ
I know you're capable.
辛い時は弱いくらいで丁度いい あたしきみの味方だよ
It's okay to be weak when it's tough, I'm on your side.
MWAH! お願い きみが欲しいの
MWAH! Please, I want you.
名前を呼んでよ いつだって会いに参上
Call my name, I'll always come running.
きみはひとりか？ それは違う ひとりじゃない もういいでしょう
Are you alone? That's not right, you're not alone, it's okay now.
ソロプレイはお仕舞いなんだったたてば
Solo play ends here.
きみがどんなときも あたし側にいるわ
Even when you're in any state, I'll be by your side.
いつも見守っているわ
I'm always watching over you,
そうよ 怖くないのよ
yes, there's nothing to fear.
MWAH! お願い きみが欲しいの
MWAH! Please, I want you.
慰めさせて ベストフレンド 愛の才能で
Let me comfort you, Best Friend, with the talent of love.
泣いてくれるかい？ きみの辛い抱きしめたい ねえいいでしょう？
Will you cry for me? I want to embrace your pain, hey, it's okay, right?
わけあって乗り越えたいんだったたてば
I want to share it and overcome it.
MWAH! お願い きみが欲しいの
MWAH! Please, I want you.
笑い飛ばしてホップステップ さあ最高で
Laugh it off, hop step, it's the best.
泣いてくれるかい？ きみに重い不安や悩み ねえいいでしょう？
Will you cry for me? Your heavy anxieties and worries, hey, it's okay, right?
吸い取って救いたいんだったたてば
I want to suck it out and save you.
ねえあたし知ってるよ
Hey, I know,
きみがひとり“涙”してるの知ってるよ
I know you're crying alone.
グスングスン凹んでさ 弱音ヒトカラ in the night
Sniffling and depressed, singing your weakness alone in the night.
ずっと一緒コース もっと泣いたって
Staying together forever, cry even more if you want.
何度だって受け止めてあげる
I'll catch it every time for you.
もう我慢しないで出してってば
Don't hold it in anymore, just let it all out.
さあ！
Now!
はい！ということで、新衣装です！
Yes! So, here's my new outfit!
みんな可愛い？
Do you think it's cute, everyone?
気になると思うけど、紹介はあとで。
I'm sure you're curious, but the introduction will be later.
先にゲストの方と歌うよ。どうぞ！
First, I'll sing with the next guest. Come on!
ときのそら お披露目誕生日 2026
[Title: Tokino Sora Birthday Party 2026]
GUEST 響咲リオナ
[Guest: Hibiki Riona]
僕等よ はじまれ
Let us start,
青く青く 果てまで
blue, blue, until the end.
拍動
[Song: Hakudou]
蘭の底 目を開けたバースデイ
A birthday where I opened my eyes at the bottom of the orchid
ホームシックにやられそうなバス停
A bus stop that feels like it's getting homesick
何処に居たって足りない 命は一つずつ足りない
No matter where you are, it's not enough,
each life is not enough
未だ 羽ばたくのは脳内にて
Still, flapping wings in the brain
終わらないで 未だ 不思議な夢を見る
Don't end, still, dreaming a strange dream
二人なら 何処までも行けると どうしてか 信じたくなる
If it's the two of us, I wonder why,
I want to believe we can go anywhere
跳ねる鼓動 誰を呼ぶの ベルの音
Beating heart, who are you calling?
The sound of a bell
座して待てど春夏秋冬 孵化は自分主導
Even if I wait and sit, the four seasons,
hatching is my own initiative
あっという間に終わる祭りを前に 恐れさえも笑い合おう
Let's laugh together at the fear before
the festival that ends in no time
共に在ろう
Let's exist together,
至って不完全体 故に面白くなってきた
quite an imperfect body,
so it's become interesting.
空腹の夜を越え 空白に願い唱え
Overcoming the hungry night,
singing prayers to the void
諦め尽くされた世界を 君とふたり占めに転げ廻る
Rolling around, taking the world that was given up on
for just the two of us
混ざり合い、そして生まれ変わるような
Mixing together, and as if being reborn,
きっと僕達だけが成せる パレード
surely it's a parade only we can accomplish.
絶対 証明したい 進化したい 才能超えた新形態
Absolutely, I want to prove it, I want to evolve,
a new form beyond talent
さあ 想像次第 「どうなりたい?"
Come on, depending on your imagination
"What do you want to become?"
斯くも現実は不可能を敷き詰めたがり
Thus, reality likes to fill itself with the impossible
過去の惜別と睨めっこしたって憂うばかり
Even if I stare at the farewells of the past,
I only feel melancholic
今はそこに君が居る 未知なるバージョン
Now you are there, an unknown version
覚醒前夜 まだ名も無きヒーロー 行こうか
The eve of awakening,
still a nameless hero, shall we go?
僕等よ はじまれ
Let us start,
青く青く 果てまで
blue, blue, until the end.
至って不完全体 故に面白くなってきた
Quite an imperfect body,
so it's become interesting.
空腹の夜を越え 空白に願い唱え
Overcoming the hungry night,
singing prayers to the void
諦め尽くされた世界を 君とふたり占めに転げ廻る
Rolling around, taking the world that was given up on
for just the two of us
混ざり合い、そして生まれ変わるような
Mixing together, and as if being reborn,
きっと僕達こそが成せる パレード
surely it's a parade only we can accomplish.
不完全体、美しきパレード
An imperfect body, a beautiful parade.
はい、というわけで、ゲストのリオナちゃんに来てもらいました！
Alright, so Hibiki Riona has joined us as a guest!
はーい！
Hello!
東北の方で地震があったみたいですが、大丈夫でしょうか？
It seems there was an earthquake in the Tohoku region.
Is everyone okay?
東北の方、身の回りの安全を優先でお願いいします。気をつけるんだよー
To everyone in Tohoku, please prioritize
your safety. Stay safe!
気をつけてくださいー
Please be careful!
そして、次のゲストはリオナちゃんです！
And our next guest is Riona-chan!
はーい！Flow Glowのリーダー、響咲リオナです！ぷらぶらー。よろしくお願いします！
Yes! I'm the leader of Flow Glow, Hibiki Riona!
Pura-pura! Nice to meet you!
そして、そら先輩、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
And Sora-senpai, happy birthday!
ありがとうございまーす！嬉しい！
Thank you so much! I'm so happy!
今日はね、あの、最近めちゃくちゃ仲いいっていうのと、やっぱり...
Today, well, since we've been getting along so well
lately, and...
めっちゃ仲いいですもんね！仲いい！
We really have been, haven't we! We're close!
歌とダンスといえば、今はリオナちゃんってイメージがあって。
When it comes to singing and dancing,
I have this strong image of Riona-chan right now.
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
一緒に、あの、歌いたいと思って、呼んじゃいました！
I really wanted to sing together, so I invited you!
本当に嬉しかったです、呼んでもらえた時！
I was truly happy when you invited me!
イェーイ！それよりそれより！
Yay! But more importantly!
そら先輩！なんですか、新衣装じゃないですか！
Sora-senpai! Look at that, you're in a new outfit!
そら先輩、めちゃくちゃ可愛い！
Sora-senpai, you're so cute!
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you so much!
どんな衣装なんですか？
What kind of outfit is it?
こちらはですね、去年出したアルバムの『パルス』っていうジャケットで、使った衣装なんですけど...
This is the outfit I used for the cover of my album
"Pulse," which was released last year...
実際にライブでも着たいと思って仕立てていただきました！
I actually wanted to wear it at a live performance, so I had it made!
あら、もうそんな、そらともさんも「ピュ～！」って感じじゃないですか？
Oh, wouldn't Sora-tomo be like "Pyuu!" about that?
「ピュ～！」って感じになっちゃうかもしれない。
They might indeed feel "Pyuu!"
じゃあ、シロさんを見習って、いろはが来た意味を今から私もやっていこうと思うんですけど。
Well, following Shiro-san's example, I'm going to show why Iroha is here today.
何ですか？
What is it?
ま、みんなもね、写真がいっぱい撮りたいと思うんですけど。
Well, everyone wants to take lots of photos, I think.
そうですね。
That's true.
いろは直伝のセクシーポーズ写真、どうですか？
How about some sexy pose photos, taught directly by Iroha?
おお！
Oh!
やるやる！スクショ大会。
I'll do it! A screenshot session.
こんな素敵な大会...
Such a wonderful session...
大会です、もうこれは。
It's a session, definitely.
大会だったんだ。
It was a session.
あのセクシーなポーズを直伝... 直伝？
I'll teach you sexy poses directly... directly?
直伝。
Directly.
伝授するので。
I'll pass them on.
それをね、そらともさんに写真撮ってもらうという回で。私、もう画面外で...
This is a segment for Sora-tomo to take photos. But I'll be off-screen...
え、何で？
Eh, why?
後で一緒に撮るの！
We'll take them together later!
あ、OKです。
Ah, OK.
じゃあ、まず。やっぱいろはといえば、あ、これ。いろはといえば、もうこれですから。
Then, first. As expected of Iroha... oh, this. When you think of Iroha, it's this.
これできるかな？ちょっと...
Can I do this? A bit...
これちょっと、あ、ちょっと足をこう...
This is a bit... oh, put your leg like this...
私的にちょっと、いろいろアウト。
For me, it's a bit... various things are out of bounds.
こういうのどうですか？こういうの。
How about this? Something like this.
こういうのね。いろははね、行きますからどっか。
Like this, right. Iroha is going to move out of the way.
あ、いいですね！いいですね、いいですね！
Ah, that's good! Nice, nice!
ちょっと右手を前に出しちゃったりして。あ、いい！いいですね、いいですね！
Try putting your right hand forward a bit. Ah, good! Nice, nice!
あ、ちょっと、あ、いい！上手い！
Ah, a bit, oh, good! You're good!
あれ？そら先輩セクシーの才能がかなりあるんじゃないですか？
Wait? Sora-senpai, don't you have quite a talent for being sexy?
おお、素晴らしい！
Oh, wonderful!
え、あとはどうしようかな？
Eh, what else should we do?
ちょっと...
Wait...
あ、やだ、いいの？それ。
Oh no, is that okay?
ふふふ。そういうことじゃないの、セクシーって。
Hehehe. That's not what sexy means.
上手い。ちょっと教える必要なかったですよ、これ。
Good. There was no need to teach you, really.
あ、上手い、ちょっと、あ、ちょっと。後ろからのアングルめっちゃいいな。
Ah, good, wait, ah, a bit. The angle from behind is really good.
ちょっと！楽しんでないでよ。
Hey! Don't just stand there enjoying it.
あ、ごめん。
Ah, sorry.
あとなんか、こういうのとかね。ヤッホーみたいな。
And then, something like this. Like "Yahoo!"
後ろからの、イェー。
From behind, yeah.
あ、いいですね、いいですね、可愛い！色とりどりでめっちゃ綺麗ですね。
Ah, nice, nice, cute! It's so colorful and beautiful.
そうなの、このグラデーションが入ってて可愛いんだよ。
Right, this gradient is so cute.
めっちゃ可愛い！
So cute!
え、じゃあ一緒に撮ってくれますか？
Eh, then will you take a photo with me?
もちろんですよ。
Of course.
イェーイ。そらいろポーズ考えようって言ったのに、全然考えられなかった。
Yay. I said we should think of a Sora-Iroha pose, but we couldn't think of one at all.
なんか、クマと、なんかいろはっぽいポーズがあって。
Like, there's a bear pose and an Iroha-like pose.
なんかいろはの公式ポーズがこれなんですけど。
Like, Iroha's official pose is this.
私はこうなんだよね。
Mine is like this.
そう、だから、そしたならなんか...
Yeah, so, then maybe...
ほぼ似てるみたい。
They're almost similar.
ほぼ一緒だ、クマと手が合ってる。
They're almost the same, the bear and the hand match.
こう、これがいいんじゃないかって思ってるんですけど、皆さんどうですか？
Like, I think this is good, what do you all think?
そらいろポーズ。
Sorairo pose.
クマと忍。
Bear and Shinobi.
クマと...
Bear and...
あんきもと忍。
Ankimo and Shinobi.
え、あとあれですよ。最近私のこと飲んでるって本当ですか？
Eh, and there's that. Is it true you've been "drinking" me lately?
そう。
Yes.
いろは錠を。貧血のいろは錠を。すごく助かっています。
Iroha tablets. The Iroha tablets for anemia. They're helping me a lot.
あ、本当ですか？じゃあ、もういつでも呼び出してください。
Oh, really? Then, call me anytime.
いろは座りに行くんで。
Iroha will come and sit by you.
あ、ありがとうございます。そら先輩どうぞ。
Ah, thank you. Sora-senpai, here you go.
あれ？吸い込まれる！
Wait? I'm being sucked in!
どうしたの、どうしたの？そら先輩、助けて！
What's wrong? What's wrong? Sora-senpai, help me!
痛かった。
That hurt.
ほら、みんな、みんなそれをやっていくんだ。
Look, everyone, everyone is going to do that.
みんなそれをやっていくんだ。
Everyone is going to do that.
でもね、いろはちゃんとは本当に仲が良くて、いつもね、よく会うんですけど。
But, I'm really good friends with Iroha-chan, and we always meet often.
普段と変わらない、可愛い感じでしたね。
She was her usual cute self.
私が消えましたね、ごめんなさい。
I disappeared, sorry.
お水を飲みに行っていました。はい。
I went to drink some water. Yes.
というわけで、続いてのゲストは... もう誰だか分かるよね？この人です！
So, the next guest is... You already know who it is, right? It's this person!
ときのそら お披露目誕生日 2026
[Tokino Sora 3D Debut Birthday 2026]
GUEST 風真いろは
[GUEST: Kazama Iroha]
ヒビカセ
作詞：Reol 作曲：Giga
[Song: Hibikase]
[Lyrics: Reol | Music: Giga]
真夜中に告ぐ 音の警告
A sound gives its warning in the middle of the night
協和音に酔う 午前零時
I'm intoxicated by the consonance at midnight
あなたが触れる 光 増す熱
With your touch, a light, an increasing fever
指先に踊らされ
You have me dancing on your fingertip
感覚 即 体感
I have an intuition, suddenly, a sensation
寝静まる夜 二人だけの密
Our secret in the sleeping night
体感 即 快感
I have a sensation, suddenly, a pleasant feeling
重なる波形に魅了されていく
I'm fascinated by the overlapping waveforms
忘れないでね わたしの声を
Don't forget my voice
ヒビカセ
[Song: Hibikase]
忘れないでね わたしの声を
Don't forget my voice
画面越しでいい ちゃんと愛して
I don't care if it's through the screen, love me properly
ヴァーチャルだって 突き放さないで
Even if I'm virtual, don't push me away
あなたの音に まだ溺れていたい
I still want to drown in your sound
覚えていてね わたしの声を
Remember my voice
あなたがくれた この身すべてを
And everything of this body you gave me
見つめ合う あなたと二人
We look at each other, alone with you
重ねた息と音とヒビカセ
Make our breath and sound resonate
真夜中に問う 冷え切った熱
A completely chilled heat questions in the middle of the night
待ち続けてる 午前零時
I'm still waiting at midnight
鏡写しに 飽和していく
I'm saturated in the reflection from the mirror
知らない音が伝う
A sound I don't know is sent my way
感覚 即 体感
I have an intuition, suddenly, a sensation
寝静まる夜と息遣い揃う
The sleeping night and our breathing laid out in front of us
体感 即 快感
I have a sensation, suddenly, a pleasant feeling
錆びたロジック 「今一度」を焦がれる
Rusted logic, I long for "just this once"
忘れないでね わたしの声を
Don't forget my voice
次元も越えて 飛ばすシグナル
My signal crosses dimensions
ヴァーチャルだなんて言わないで
Don't call me virtual
あなたの音に まだ愛されていたい
I still want to be loved by your sound
覚えていてね わたしの声を
Remember my voice
あなたがくれた この身すべてを
And everything of this body you gave me
言の葉と初の音が交わる
Words and a first sound mix together
この息と音とヒビカセ
Make our breath and sound resonate
あなたの生んだ音に ただ恋をしていたの
I just fell in love with the sound you produced
悲しみ 怒り 甘心 すべて打ち鳴らす
Sadness, anger, satisfaction, all ringing out
絶えず叫ぶ 声連ねる
Constantly shouting, voices lining up
余熱交ぜる 愛、絶 艶めく
Our remaining heat mixing, love and sorrow seem alluring
絶えず叫ぶ 声連ねる
Constantly shouting, voices lining up
余熱交ぜる 愛、絶 艶めく
Our remaining heat mixing, love and sorrow seem alluring
魅了されていく
I'm fascinated
忘れないでね わたしの声を
Don't forget my voice
画面越しでいい ちゃんと愛して
I don't care if it's through the screen, love me properly
ヴァーチャルだって 突き放さないで
Even if I'm virtual, don't push me away
あなたの音に まだ溺れていたい
I still want to drown in your sound
覚えていてね わたしの声を
Remember my voice
あなたがくれた この身すべてを
And everything of this body you gave me
見つめ合う あなたと二人
We look at each other, alone with you
重ねた息と音をヒビカセ
Make our breath and sound resonate
あなたの初の音 この声聴かせ
Let me hear your first sound, this voice...
オトヒビカセ
Make the sound resonate
はい！ということで最後のゲストは、いろはちゃんでーす！
Yes! And so, the last guest is Iroha-chan!
いえーい！ホロックスの、強い、イケメン、速い、
Yay! HoloX's strong, cool, fast,
かっこいい、なんかすごい、風真いろはでーす！
cool, somehow amazing, Kazama Iroha!
いえーい！
Yay!
おかしいなー、おかしいなー
That's strange... that's strange...
そら先輩！
Sora-senpai!
なに？
What?
お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Happy Birthday!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
おかしいなー
That's strange...
何がおかしいんだい？
What's strange?
リハーサル日まではあんなにメロついてくれてたのに...
Until the rehearsal day, you were so head over heels for me...
（笑）すご、じゃ、今日、今日のために整えてくれたってこと？
(Laughs) Wow, so you prepared yourself just for today?
今日のために、ちょっとあの整えさせていただきました
For today, I prepared myself a bit.
あー、ありがとうございます。コメント欄のみんなもあんなにメロついてくれてたのに、
Ah, thank you. Everyone in the comments was so head over heels too...
今日は全然メロついてない...
But today no one is head over heels at all...
いやいやいや、そんなことなかったよ！「かっこいい二人とも」って書いてあったよ！
No no no, that's not true! They wrote "Both of you are cool"!
え, 本当ですか？本当に？
Eh, really? Really?
本当に！
Really!
え、ちょっともう一回見たいから「かっこいい」って書いて。
Eh, I want to see it again so please write "cool".
かっこいいって。みんな「かっこいい」って書いて。
Write "cool". Everyone write "cool".
「かわいい、かわいい、かわいい、かわいい」
"Cute, cute, cute, cute"
「かわいい」は当たり前じゃん。
"Cute" is a given, right?
あ、そうだよね。
Ah, right.
そうだよね。ござるちゃんはいつでもかわいい。
Right. Gozaru-chan is always cute.
ほら、「かっこいい、かっこいい」って！
Look, "cool, cool"!
あ、ありがとうございます！
Ah, thank you!
お前たちのかっこいいが義務だとしても、風真いろは嬉しいぞ！
Even if your "cool" is obligatory, Kazama Iroha is happy!
ね、あの、一人でも記念配信で歌ってたけど、すごく良かったから一緒に歌いたいなと思って呼んじゃいました！
Right, you sang it in your anniversary stream alone too, but it was so good I wanted to sing it together so I invited you!
嬉しいー！嬉しくて、嬉しくて死んでしまう...
I'm so happy! I'm so happy, I'm so happy I'm going to die...
生きて！生きて！
Live! Live!
あ、生きてますよ、生きてますよ。
Ah, I'm alive, I'm alive.
おお、よかったよかった。
Oh, good good.
いや、でも、やっぱそら先輩といえばボカロ曲めっちゃ似合うなって思ってたんで、
But I always thought Sora-senpai really suits Vocaloid songs...
いつかやってくんないかなーって、オタクとして思ってたんですけど、
I was hoping you'd do it someday, as an otaku...
まさか自分がゲストとして呼んでもらえるなんて！
But I never expected to be invited as a guest!
こんなありがたいことがあっていいのか...
Is it okay for such a thankful thing to happen...?
いいのか？
Is it okay?
いや、一緒に2人で歌ったことがなかったから、歌ってみたくて。
No, we've never sung as a duo before,
so I really wanted to try it.
確かに。星街ティックだとね、結構ね。
True. On "Hoshimachi-tic", it happens quite a bit.
そうそう。
Yeah, exactly.
ついでにやってること多いんですけどね。
We often do it as an extra thing, though.
フェスとかでも歌ったけど3人とかだったから。デュエットってやったことがなくて。
We sang at festivals too, but in groups of three.
We've never done a proper duet.
確かに。
True.
ねー。
Right?
ありがたいお話でございまして本当に。
I'm truly grateful for this opportunity.
こちらこそ本当に。
The pleasure is all mine, really.
貴重な体験を。
A precious experience.
いやこちらこそありがとうございます本当に。
No, thank you so much, seriously.
はい。
Yes.
いや、それにしても。
But anyway...
はい。
Yes?
今日これ新衣装なんですよね。
You're wearing a new outfit today, aren't you?
そうなんですよ。新衣装なんですよ。
That's right. It's a new outfit.
新衣装なんですよね。
It's a new outfit, isn't it?
どう？
How is it?
おー。おー。
Ooh. Ooh.
いやちょっと、さっきリオーナさんがなんか結構際どいこと言っていたんですけど。
Well, earlier Riona-san was saying
some pretty risky things...
やはりね、あの、やっぱ、ちょっと、こっちのクイクイタイプオタクとして一個よろしいでしょうか。
As a curious otaku, can I ask one thing?
何でしょう。
What is it?
やはり男というものはですね、やっぱあの、一肌脱いだ姿が気になると言うものでございまして。
Men are naturally curious about
what lies beneath a layer.
あの、この隠されている純白が、あの、この姿で見れるのかっていうのがすごく気になっておりまして。
I'm very curious if we can see the pure white
hidden under this outfit.
本当に。だって、この下のなんかもう清楚感溢れるこれ絶対みんな気になるでしょ。
Seriously. I mean, everyone must be curious about
the sense of purity underneath this.
いや、オタクとして、もう気になりますよこんなの。
As an otaku, I'm just so curious about this.
そうですよね。
Right.
でも、この配信の中ではちょっとまだ見せれないかなー。
But, I might not be able to show it
just yet during this stream.
え、え、もしかして、そ、それは、脱げると言うことでござるか？
Eh, eh, does that mean...
it *can* come off?
この配信の中では見せることはないんだけど。
I won't be showing it during this stream, but...
お前たち！
You guys!
メンゲンに入れ！メンゲンに入ったら見れる可能性があるぞ！
Join the members-only! There's a chance
you can see it if you join!
はい。いや楽しみにしておりますので。
Yes. I'm looking forward to it.
こちらこそ。
Same here.
メンゲンに入れ？
Join the members-only?
入れ？
Join?
メンゲンに入れ？
Join the members-only?
すごい強制的。
So forceful.
だって、これ、脱げた姿が見れるんですよ。
I mean, you can see her with it off.
このあとも楽しみにしてますよ！
I'm looking forward to the rest of the stream!
はい！
Yes!
と言うわけで、そら先輩まだこのあとも全然続くと思うんですけど。
So, Sora-senpai, I think you're going to
continue for a while longer.
頑張ってください！
Good luck!
頑張るよ！
I'll do my best!
あの、プロとしてお待ちしておりますんで。
I'll be waiting for you as a pro.
そうだね。またあとで。
Right. See you later.
はい、プロとして。
Yes, as a pro.
プロとして。
As a pro.
あ、やばい、プロの世界に引き込まれてしまう。
Ah, no, I'm being drawn into the world of pros.
あー、プロの世界に引き込まれてしまうでござるわ。上品だから、あの、お水は出さないで！
Ah, I'm being drawn into the world of pros.
Since I'm elegant, please don't drool!
ありがとう。ありがとう。
Thank you. Thank you.
未来で待ってる。
I'll be waiting in the future.
未来で待っててくれ。
Please wait for me in the future.
指なんだ。
It's a finger.
さあ、何の、何をね、あの、またあとでってどういうことなんでしょうかね。
Now, what... what did she mean by
"later," I wonder?
はい。プロとして何のプロなんでしょうか。
Yes. As a pro, a pro of what exactly?
気になる方、後ライブに来てもらえたら嬉しいなと思います。
For those curious, I'd be happy if you could
come to the later live show.
さて。ちょっとお待ちくださいね。
Now then. Please wait a moment.
いよいよ終盤戦です。
It's finally the final stage.
お水おいしい。
Water is delicious.
いよいよ終盤戦なんですけど。
It's finally the final stage.
最後まで盛り上がっててください！
Please keep the excitement going until the end!
もしかしたら、あの子が来ちゃうかもね。
Maybe that girl will show up.
聞いてください。
Please listen.
プレイ。
Play.
プレイ / 作詞:ケンモチヒデフミ / 作曲:Giga
[Song: Play / Lyrics: Kenmochi Hidefumi / Music: Giga]
ちょけろ ちょけろ さぁ図に乗って
Fool around, fool around, come on, get cocky
いい加減にしろって やめらんないねぇ
Stop it already, but I can't stop
どうしようもねぇ 言い訳なら後で
It's hopeless, I'll think of an excuse later
考えてくれてやる
I'll give it some thought
王道とか下らねぇな毎回
The royal road is so stupid every time
自意識過剰なやつ徘徊
Self-conscious people wandering around
みんなが右往左走する間に
While everyone is running around in confusion
こちとら地に足つけてきたぜ ハイハイ
I've kept my feet on the ground, yes, yes
どうした？ みんな 浮かない顔して
What's wrong? Everyone looks so gloomy
絵空ごと大歓迎よ Diggin’ Dong Ding
Fanciful tales are very welcome, Diggin' Dong Ding
現実味ねぇよ Diggin’ Dong Ding
There's no reality, Diggin' Dong Ding
早く楽になりたい？ いつでもいいよ
Want to be at ease soon? Anytime is fine
おねんねさせたれ Nothing to do with you
I'll put you to sleep, nothing to do with you
ちょけろ ちょけろ さぁ図に乗って
Fool around, fool around, come on, get cocky
いい加減にしろって やめらんないねぇ
Stop it already, but I can't stop
はぜろ はぜろ おおおおお
Burst, burst, oh oh oh oh oh
責任だってとるよ 墓場までは
I'll even take responsibility, all the way to the grave
堂々とだけさせてくれよ
Just let me be bold
こちとらマイペースな トラブルメーカー
I'm a trouble maker at my own pace
取扱説明書 隅から隅まで 読んでおきな
Read the instruction manual from cover to cover
ヒヤッとしたってなぜか ニヤッとしちゃうのおかっしーな
I got a chill, but for some reason I find myself grinning
とめろ、とめろ とめろ、とめろ
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it
絵空ごとも大歓迎よ Diggin’ Dong Ding
Fanciful tales are also very welcome, Diggin' Dong Ding
現実味ねぇよ Diggin’ Dong Ding
There's no reality, Diggin' Dong Ding
早く楽になりたい？ いつでもいいよ
Want to be at ease soon? Anytime is fine
おねんねさせたれ Nothing to do with you
I'll put you to sleep, nothing to do with you
押せよ そのリセットボタン
Press it, that reset button
消せよ お前のその価値観
Erase it, those values of yours
どうせ 何度でも 元に戻せるなら
If you can reset it as many times as you want anyway
指くわえてみてるだけじゃ つまらないやいや
Just watching with your finger in your mouth is boring
so I’m ready 思いっきり
so I'm ready, with all my might
前ノリ気味 止まる気ない アクセルベタ踏み
Ahead of the beat, no stopping, pedal to the metal
ねぇ Are you Kidding？ ねぇ Are you Kidding？
Hey, are you kidding? Hey, are you kidding?
はい、ちょ、まって ここでストップ
Yes, wait a second, stop right here
Return to the start
ぜってーやべーよ！ 話がちげーぞ！
This is definitely bad! The story's different!
早く楽になりたい？ いつでもいいよ
Want to be at ease soon? Anytime is fine
おねんねさしたれ
I'll put you to sleep
Ah... 戻れない　ないものねだりの夢の果て
Ah... I can't return to the end of the dream, always wishing for what I don't have.
Ah... 踊っている　夢の中で
Ah... I'm dancing, even if I'm just dreaming.
戻れるかな　あの頃の自分に
Can I go back to that time again?
いや、もう戻れないから
No, I can't go back anymore.
調子に乗らせて　踊らせてみるのが
Letting myself get carried away, letting myself dance,
楽でいいのかもしれないな
maybe that's just easier.
なんてね。
Just kidding.
はい、ありがとうございました！
Yes, thank you very much!
この曲、『プレイ』を歌わせていただきました。
I just performed the song, "Play."
そして、この曲ではなんとサングラスをかけたあんきもがやってきました！
And for this song, Ankimo joined me wearing sunglasses!
どっちサングラス？
Which sunglasses are those?
わあ、取れた！
Whoa, they came off!
遊ぶんじゃないの。もういい。
Don't play with them! Fine, then.
というわけで、久々にあんきもと一緒に、なんか踊った気がするんだけど、どう？
So, I feel like I haven't danced with Ankimo in a while, but how was it?
5人目のゲスト、あんきもです！
Our fifth guest, Ankimo!
イエーイ！ある意味シークレットだったでしょ？
Yay! He was a secret in a way, right?
めっちゃ踊るじゃん。
He's dancing so much.
そしてね、まあそんな感じで。
And well, moving on.
まだね、最後にね、実はお披露目もあるんだけど。
I still have one last reveal at the end,
ここでね、まず恒例のお知らせがたくさんあるので。
but first, we have a lot of the usual announcements.
ここからはあんきもと一緒に告知していくからね。
I'll be making the announcements with Ankimo from here.
聞いてください。まずは、こちら！
Please take a look. First, this!
ときのそら 誕生日記念2026 グッズです！
[Visual: Tokino Sora Birthday Celebration 2026 Goods!]
順番に紹介していくよ。まずは、こちら！
I'll introduce them one by one. First, this!
Dream! そらとも法被。イラストはおるだん先生です。
[Dream! Soratomo Happi Coat] Illustrated by Ordan-sensei.
テーマはライブをしてる私、ということでなんとあんきももいっぱいおるんだよ。
The theme is me performing live, and look, there are lots of Ankimos too.
今までもオリジナル法被自体はストアとかで出たことはあるんですけど、
I've released original Happi coats in stores before,
自分でオリジナルで作るのは初めてだったので、
but this is the first time I've designed one myself.
ぜひライブで着てきてほしいなと思って作りました。
I made it because I really want you to wear it to my live concerts.
ぜひぜひみんな楽しんでくださいね。ライブに来てください！
Please enjoy it, everyone. Please come to the live!
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this!
「お部屋でのんびり」ワイドラバーマット！
["Relaxing in the Room" Wide Rubber Mat!]
イラストは、しわずたかし先生です。
Illustrated by Shiwazu Takashi-sensei.
テーマは部屋でファンレターを読んでいる私で、
The theme is me reading fan letters in my room.
こちらでホロカのやつにね、ちょうどいいサイズになってるので、
It's the perfect size for playing Holoka,
ホロカを遊ぶ方、ぜひぜひ一緒にね、持って行って遊んでもらえたら嬉しいなと思います。
so if you play Holoka, I'd be happy if you used it to play.
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this!
そらとおそろいスマホリング！
[Matching Smartphone Ring with Sora!]
前回販売したDJSパーカーとデザインが一緒なので、
The design is the same as the DJS hoodie sold previously,
それと一緒に合わせてスマホも私とおそろっちにしませんか、っていう感じです。
so why not match your phone with me as well?
そして続いては、こちら！
And next up is this!
そらザウルスなりきりそらちゃんぬいぐるみ！
[Sorazaurus Narikiri Sora-chan Plushie!]
みんながあまりにも「そらザウルス、そらザウルス」って言うからさ。
Because everyone kept saying "Sorazaurus, Sorazaurus."
でもそらザウルス自体を言うのはちょっと恥ずかしかったから、
But I was a bit embarrassed to say "Sorazaurus" myself,
そらちゃんぬいぐるみ、私が着ていることにするなりきりのぬいぐるみにしました。
so I made it a plushie of me wearing the costume.
しかもね、何そらザウルスって思う人、これ取るとフードが取れると、
And for those wondering, if you remove the hood,
もうピンクの衣装を着てる私みたいになるので、
I'll be wearing my pink outfit underneath.
ぜひぜひフードを取り外して可愛く持ち歩いてくれてもいいんじゃないかなと思います。
So you can remove the hood and carry it around too.
そして最後は、こちら！
And finally, this!
ASMRボイス。タイトルは「届いてるよ、きみの応援」。
[ASMR Voice] Title: "Your Cheers are Reaching Me."
部屋でファンレターを読んでいるシチュエーションになっておりますので、
It features a scenario where I'm reading fan letters in my room,
ぜひぜひ皆さん、どんな風にファンレター読んでるのかなと想像しながら聞いてもらえたら嬉しいです。
so please listen while imagining how I read them.
そして、フルセット購入特典は、こちら！
And the full set purchase bonuses are these!
直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りポストカードと特典ボイス、
A postcard with a handwritten signature and foil-stamped message, and a bonus voice.
ボイスタイトルは「誕生日を向かえて」になります。
The voice title is "Welcoming My Birthday."
というわけでですね、皆さん急がなくて大丈夫です。
So, everyone, there's no need to rush.
数量限定ではございませんので、皆さん全員分のサインを書かせていただきます。
It's not limited in quantity, so I'll be signing them for everyone.
いくらでも書きますので、ぜひぜひ皆さん、たくさんの人にグッズを買ってもらえたら私はとても嬉しい、
I'll sign as many as needed, so I'd be so happy if many people bought them,
なので、よろしくお願いいたします。
so please support me.
以上、ときのそら誕生日記念2026グッズでした！みんなよろしくね。
That's all for the Tokino Sora Birthday Celebration 2026 goods! Thank you all.
続いてのお知らせは、こちら！
Next up is this announcement!
11月ワンマンライブの「ときのそら生誕記念」先行チケット販売開始！
Pre-sales for the "Tokino Sora Birthday Celebration" solo live in November have begun!
ぴあアリーナMMの先行チケットが本日から始まっております。
Early ticket sales for Pia Arena MM start today.
ファンクラブに入ってる人しかできないじゃないかって言ってた人、
For those who thought only fan club members could get them,
本日から一般で皆さんも、販売が開始されておりますので、
general sales for everyone have also started today.
ぜひぜひ、もう12時から開始されております。
They've already started since 12:00 PM.
応募していただけたら嬉しいです。みんなでぴあアリーナでライブ楽しもう！
I'd be happy if you applied. Let's enjoy the live at Pia Arena together!
さらに、こちら！
Furthermore, this!
その現地チケットの特典でもらえるホロカのお披露目！
The reveal of the Holoka card you get as a bonus for venue tickets!
ライブの来場者特典として、限定ホロカが1枚配られます。
One limited Holoka card will be given to live attendees as a bonus.
全2種類のうち1枚をランダムでお渡しするのですが、そちらの1枚を公開です。
One of two types will be given at random, and we're revealing one of them.
私が描き下ろすということで、もう一個の方は、まだ。
I'm drawing them, and the other one is still a secret for now.
なので、ぜひこちらのほうでちょっと...
So, please, with this...
満足していただけないでしょうか？
I hope you'll be satisfied with it.
そして、10周年ライブを記念して、こちら！
And to celebrate the 10th anniversary live, this!
スペシャルテレビCM放送決定！
[Text: Special TV CM to be aired!]
ということで、本日の22時半から23時の間...
So, tonight between 22:30 and 23:00...
TOKYO MXさんのところで流れます。
it will be aired on TOKYO MX.
一度だけなものなので、ぜひ見てくれると...
It's a one-time thing, so I'd be happy if you watched it.
嬉しいなと思いますよ。よろしくお願いします！
I'd really appreciate it. Thank you!
そしてそして、最後のお知らせがこちら！
And finally, the last announcement is this!
お待たせしました。こちらです！
Thank you for waiting. Here it is!
新曲「決意のソラへ」です！
It's my new song, "Ketsui no Sora e"!
私的にはなんか、エモい感じの曲とかね、泣き曲かなって思ったんだけど...
Personally, I thought it was an emotional or a tear-jerking song...
でもディレクターさん的にはもう、泣き曲とかエモとかそういう感じじゃない...
But the director said it's not just a tear-jerker or emotional...
熱い曲、みたいな感じで。オープニングにふさわしい感じの...
It's a passionate song. Something fit for an opening...
熱い曲を作ったつもり、みたいなことを言っていたので...
He said he intended to make a passionate song.
このあとね、MVがプレミア公開も予定されているので...
The MV is scheduled for a premiere later...
各種音楽サイトでも配信もされています。ぜひたくさん...
and it's also available on various music sites. Please...
聴いてもらえたら嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you listened to it a lot!
はい、というわけでね、とっても楽しかったんですけど、いかがだったでしょうか？
Alright, I had a great time, but how was it for you?
告知がね、あの、洪水のようにやってきたと思うので...
The announcements came like a flood...
あとでみんな確認してもらえると、嬉しいなと思います！
so I'd appreciate it if everyone could check them later!
えーそしてですね、メイン会場は21時半から、アフターライブがあるんですけど...
And there will be an after-live at the main venue starting from 21:30...
スペシャルあん肝がね、なんとね、見れるかもしれないんだって！
where you might get to see a special Ankimo!
スペシャルだよ、スペシャル！
It's special, special!
このサングラスあん肝もスペシャルではあるんだけど、さらにスペシャルなあん肝が...
This sunglasses Ankimo is special, but an even more special Ankimo...
見れるかもしれない。そしてね...
might be seen. And...
さっきも言いました、この放送では...
like I said before, in this broadcast...
まあちょっとまだ言えないかなーって言ってたもの、ありますよね？
there was something I said I couldn't talk about yet, right?
いろんな撮影会しましょう！というわけで、ここまで付き合ってくれてありがとう！
Let's have various photo sessions! Anyway, thanks for staying with me!
あん肝バイバイ！
Bye-bye, Ankimo!
サングラス似合ってたぞ！
The sunglasses looked good on you!
みんな吸い込まれていく...
Everyone's being sucked in...
はい、というわけでね、みなさんいかがだったでしょうか？
Alright, so, how was it everyone?
そしてこんなにね、えーいつもの情報の洪水が起こっていると思うんですが...
I think there's a flood of information as usual...
ぜひぜひ皆さんあとで見て、もらえたら嬉しいです。
but I'd be happy if everyone checked it out later.
えー最後はですね、こんだけ「決意のソラへ」と言っておいて歌わないのは...
Finally, after talking so much about "Ketsui no Sora e," it wouldn't be right not to sing it...
どうかなと思いますので、新曲で締めたいと思います！
so I'd like to close with the new song!
それでは聞いてください、「決意のソラへ」！
Please listen, "Ketsui no Sora e"!
一度きりの私の物語は
My story, just once,
運命を超えて煌めくんだ
shines beyond fate.
行こう
Let's go.
皆さん本日はありがとうございました！
Thank you all for today!
とっても楽しかったー！
I had so much fun!
ねぇ 私より私のことを
Hey, understanding me
わかってくれる キミの存在が
better than I understand myself, your presence...
臆病で泣き虫な心に
cast a magic called courage
勇気と言う魔法をかけたの
upon my cowardly and tearful heart.
チクタク 時計の針だけが進む
Tick-tock, the hands of the clock just keep moving.
立ち止まってちゃダメだ
It's no use stopping;
ソラ転び八起きがお決まりでしょ
falling and getting up is the norm, isn't it?
一つ一つ重ねてきた
Like turning the pages
大切なアルバムをめくるように
of an important album we've layered one by one,
一つ一つ叶えてきた今日まで
you were there for everything up until today
その全てにキミがいてくれた
that we've made come true one by one.
終わりのない夢を
This endless dream...
ずっとずっとずっとずっと 追いかけて行こう
Let's chase it forever and ever.
行こう
Let's go.
Xのトレンド入りも果たしたそうで...
I heard we even trended on X...
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ねぇ ここで笑い合えることが
Hey, being able to laugh here
何よりも大事な真実
is the most important truth of all.
チクチク イタズラなハートが痛む
Prickly, my mischievous heart hurts.
空回り空回り
Spinning in the air, spinning...
思考回路フル回転で よーいどん
my thinking circuits are at full rotation. Ready, set, go!
泣いて泣いて泣いた夜も
Even the nights I cried and cried
大切な人生のストーリーだから
are an important story of my life, so...
夢を 夢で 終わらせたくないんだ
I don't want to let my dreams just be dreams
まだ見ぬ景色を 見に行こうよ
Let's go see the scenery we haven't seen yet
もっともっと かがやいて
Shine more and more
高く高く 飛び立とう
Let's fly higher and higher
奇跡さえも越えて
Even beyond miracles
みなさん たくさんのコメント ありがとうございます！
Everyone, thank you so much for all the comments!
一つ一つ 重ねてきた
One by one, we've layered them together
未来地図のページを めくるように
Like turning the pages of a map to the future
泣いて泣いて 泣いた夜も
Even the nights I cried and cried
大切な人生の ストーリーだから
Are part of my precious life story
夢を 夢で 終わらせたくないんだ
I don't want to let my dreams just be dreams
まだ見ぬ景色を 見に行こうよ
Let's go see the scenery we haven't seen yet
終わりのない歌を
An endless song...
キミにキミにキミへと届け
...I send to you, to you, to you
ずっとずっと 誓うの
I swear forever and ever
決意のソラへ
To the sky of determination
行こう
Let's go
本当に みんなのおかげで 最高の誕生日になりました！
Truly, thanks to everyone, this was the best birthday ever!
みんなのこと 大好きだよ！
I love you all so much!
次のライブも 来てね！
Please come to the next live too!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
告知あり / ときのそら お披露目誕生日 2026
[Announcement Inside] / Tokino Sora Birthday Party 2026